So far in this lesson we've been talking about the techniques that we need to have really good discussions.
到目前为止，在本课中，我们一直在讨论我们需要进行非常好的讨论的技术。
Now we need to look at actually some phrases that we can use to ask these questions.
现在我们需要看一些我们可以用来问这些问题的短语。
So let's let's look at these.
那么让我们来看看这些。
This is a basic one but we could just say what do you think are the basic reasons.
这是一个基本原因，但我们只能说您认为基本原因是什么。
What do you think are the most important reasons.
你认为最重要的原因是什么。
What do you think are the best ways.
你认为最好的方法是什么。
All of these things are ways to get somebodies mind moving.
所有这些都是让人们动心的方法。
Why do you think the Internet but other than that whatever the topic is OK you're just getting their
你为什么认为互联网，但除此之外，无论主题是好的，你只是得到他们的
ideas.
想法。
So what do you think are what do you think is and why do you think.
所以你认为什么是你认为是什么以及你为什么这么认为。
How could people or how could we you could use other things there.
人怎么可能或我们怎么能在那里使用其他东西。
You don't have to use people.
你不必使用人。
This one how could people how could you How could I.
这一个人怎么可能你怎么可能我。
How could we.
我们怎么可能。
Is a way to get somebody to give you a possible solution a possible answer to a problem.
是一种让某人给你一个可能的解决方案一个问题的可能答案的方法。
And how could people get a really good education without needing to borrow eighty thousand dollars a
一个人不用借八万块钱，怎么能得到真正好的教育呢？
year to go to a great university.
一年去上一所好大学。
OK so what do you think about that.
好的，那么您对此有何看法。
Give me an idea.
给我一个想法。
How could we do this.
我们怎么能这样做。
And I'm not going to go into that.
我不打算讨论这个。
It's just a question that we could ask if we want to discuss that.
如果我们想讨论这个问题，我们可以问这个问题。
And I've had that conversation many times I've asked that question many times.
我已经多次进行过这样的对话，我也多次问过这个问题。
If you were that debt what would you do to if you were the president of your country.
如果你是那个债务，如果你是你的国家的总统，你会怎么做。
What would you do to solve the issue of hunger in poor areas.
您将如何解决贫困地区的饥饿问题。
Now we're thinking about a hypothetical.
现在我们正在考虑一个假设。
Remember we talked about a hypothetical question which is where we imagine it right.
请记住，我们讨论了一个假设性问题，我们认为它是正确的。
If you were the president where you're not the president but if you were what would you do if people
如果你是总统但你不是总统但如果你是总统你会怎么做
who smoked didn't need to worry about getting cancer what would be the result.
吸烟的人不必担心会患上癌症会是什么结果。
Would they still smoke or not.
他们还会抽烟还是不抽烟。
What would smoking be really popular.
什么会吸烟真的很受欢迎。
Would everybody do it or not.
每个人都会做还是不做。
Right.
正确的。
We can think about these questions.
我们可以思考这些问题。
What would you do is even more open than the smoking one because it's asking someone to describe an
你会做什么比吸烟更开放，因为它要求某人描述一个
action.
行动。
OK.
好的。
So then they're talking about steps.
所以他们在谈论步骤。
First I would do this and then I would do this.
首先我会这样做，然后我会这样做。
And it's fun.
这很有趣。
It's really fun to explore hypotheticals.
探索假设真的很有趣。
So using this what would you do if is a really powerful way to get somebodies brain moving.
因此，如果使用它是一种让某人大脑移动的非常有效的方法，你会怎么做。
OK.
好的。
What do you think about now of course this is the most basic type of question.
你现在怎么想当然这是最基本的问题。
What do you think about a.
你怎么看a。
And you can just say the topic.
你可以说这个话题。
What do you think about smoking in public.
您如何看待在公共场所吸烟。
Now people are going to give a very open answer a very wide answer so you can use that in any conversation
现在人们会给出一个非常开放的答案，一个非常广泛的答案，这样你就可以在任何对话中使用它
at the beginning.
一开始。
Just be careful with that one.
小心那个。
What do you think about smoking in public.
您如何看待在公共场所吸烟。
What do you think about poverty in your country but you have to know that when you ask that question
您如何看待您所在国家/地区的贫困，但当您提出这个问题时，您必须知道
some people might not have a great thing to say about it because maybe they haven't thought about it
有些人可能对此没有什么好说的，因为也许他们没有考虑过
before because of that.
之前因为那个。
Maybe the topic will go that way.
也许话题会这样。
Maybe the topic will go to and die.
也许这个话题会去死。
You do have to be careful but it can also be a way to really get a conversation going and not push the
您确实必须小心，但这也可以成为真正进行对话而不是推动对话的一种方式
person you ask in this direction or that direction give them total freedom first and then follow them
你在这个方向或那个方向问的人首先给他们完全的自由，然后跟随他们
go with them based on where they want to go.
根据他们想去的地方和他们一起去。
That's also a good way to to keep a conversation going to follow another person's interests.
这也是保持对话遵循另一个人的兴趣的好方法。